import React from 'react'

let paranormal = {
    title: 'Paranormal',
    questions: [
        {   
            question: "This is another word for Bigfoot",
            answers: ["Giant Man", "Sasquatch", "Neanderthal", "Ramapithecus"],
            correct: "Sasquatch"
        },
        {   
            question: "This country is home to the Nazca lines",
            answers: ["Congo", "Antartica", "Peru", "China"],
            correct: "Peru"
        },
        {   
            question: "If you wanted to see Nessie, you'd go here",
            answers: ["Scotland", "Finland", "Wales", "Norway"],
            correct: "Scotland"
        },
        {   
            question: "The highly active region of paranormal activities called Bermuda is this shape",
            answers: ["Circle", "Triangle", "Square", "Crescent"],
            correct: "Triangle"
        },
        {   
            question: "This squadron of planes mysteriously disappeared over the Atlantic",
            answers: ["Flight 105", "Flight 19", "Flight 38", "Flight 5"],
            correct: "Flight 19"
        },
        {   
            question: "Area 51 is located in this state",
            answers: ["Texas", "New Mexico", "Nevada", "Arizona"],
            correct: "Nevada"
        },
        {   
            question: "Ogopogo is a lake monster in this country",
            answers: ["Canada", "United States", "Spain", "Brazil"],
            correct: "Canada"
        },
        {   
            question: "The mothman is associated with this bridge",
            answers: ["Golden Gate", "London", "Silver", "Story"],
            correct: "Silver"
        },
        {   
            question: "Waterskiing was invented after Ralph Samuelson said he saw this creature",
            answers: ["Pepie", "Nessie", "Ogopogo", "Okie"],
            correct: "Pepie"
        },
        {   
            question: "The Florida Everglades house this paranormal creature",
            answers: ["Skunk Ape", "Mothman", "Yeti", "Bell Witch"],
            correct: "Skunk Ape"
        },
        {   
            question: "This creature is said to live in Enfield",
            answers: ["Poltergeist", "Sasquatch", "Chupacabra", "Dog headed man"],
            correct: "Poltergeist"
        },
        {   
            question: "This creature is reptile like with spines and is known as the goatsucker",
            answers: ["Wererats", "Dijinns", "Chupacabra", "Jaculus"],
            correct: "Chupacabra"
        },
        {   
            question: "Mother Leeds is accused of giving birth to which creature",
            answers: ["Jersey Devil", "Jabberwocky", "Arion", "Mothman"],
            correct: "Jersey Devil"
        },
        {   
            question: "This creature terrorized New Delhi in 2001",
            answers: ["Monkey Man", "Skunk Ape", "Dog Man", "Chupacabra"],
            correct: "Monkey Man"
        },
        {   
            question: "This occurrence caused President Truman to call the air force for an explanation",
            answers: ["Mothman incident", "Orange lights", "Ghost Rockets", "Roswell Crash"],
            correct: "Orange lights"
        },
        {   
            question: "This president filed a UFO sighting",
            answers: ["Carter", "Ford", "Clinton", "Bush"],
            correct: "Carter"
        },
        {   
            question: "The Berwyn Mountain crash is in this country",
            answers: ["Canada", "Switzerland", "UK", "Soviet Union"],
            correct: "UK"
        },
        {   
            question: "This famous couple was the first to claim to have been abducted by aliens",
            answers: ["The Jones", "The Campbells", "The Hills", "The Smiths"],
            correct: "The Hills"
        }
    ]
}

export default paranormal